o_k o_k so eso these are new right ?
o_k .
those are new o_k .
this is .
alright she left these here for you to I guess process them or whatever .
mmhm .
right right .
whatever her it' she needs to sign it .
o_k .
o_k ?
eh .
so everything is the same except the finances ?
everything is the same porque we switched it from Citizens to Universal .
oh yeah o_k .
everything' been switched .
o_k o_k .
entonces .
oh that' right uhuh ok .
this is gonna go with with the application to Universal this is going to go .
o_k .
and then this is and then we're going to open a new file for finance which is something I think you guys don't have .
right no .
sí todo estaba junto .
o_k .
well everything was together pero I for the past couple of things yo no mandé esto .
yo no mandé el contrato .
o_k .
that' why en en los faxes que me venían eso like came in .
that' why lo están pidiendo .
exacto .
so we're gonna open new files .
mmhm .
o_k he only has one one thing so we would do him en los folders más finitos .
o_k .
and the blue ones that you gave me there right ?
not we don't have to do the blue .
we can do .
oh any .
yeah she she just said yeah para empezar .
o_k o_k .
so what you do is you put the policy on the right and the correspondence on the left .
mmhm .
o_k .
so ya tú sabes aquí está todo junto .
mmhm .
sí sí que a la hora de buscar it' o_k .
we're not .
we're and now it' going to be individual .
alright .
o_k o_k .
o_k ?
so that that'll work .
right .
y entonces o_k so then we'll do that .
so ...
so I'll I'll put everything together and make a copy of everything .
mmhm .
y después esto va a ir separado que es en otro folder .
right .
which is gonna be a finance folder .
a finance o_k .
you know so that' how this one is gonna be .
so I'm gonna leave that out there o_k .
so pretty much yo creo que todas era esto .
o_k .
este se formó ...
tremendo lío .
tremenda lío .
really ?
big time yeah .
pero bueno eso eso eso es y después te lo .
mmhm laugh .
+, te lo cuento .
entonces también este este se va a tener que abrir in a commercial folder .
mmhm .
o_k .
o_k ?
which the commercials are different as well right ?
yeah pero but if it' like como ese que es just a G_O lo hacemos en el finito para no coger the .
oh yeah .
sí pero no los big ones .
right .
o_k .
sí únicamente que they have like everything like homeowners insurance mumble whatever flood .
then we do the big one .
yeah .
o_k .
um o_k what else ?
entonces nada es Julia Pérez .
o_k .
Morales Muñoz we just redid again .
pero ...
ajá .
so este es signature and the processing of the thing .
o_k .
so todo está en finance .
yes .
o_k .
so .
and these are all like renewals that came in or ?
oh .
estos estos son los los problemáticos .
ah que tuvieron que rescribirlos .
todo ?
because she forgot this .
really ?
cuando se hizo cuando cuando se arregló el problema she forgot normally .
ajá .
y pasó un mes .
todo el mundo cogió cancelación .
y y la y no tenían la explicación en ?
oh my god what a mess .
no .
no había nada nada nada nada nada .
yeah yeah so imagínate viernes aquí .
holy shoot .
cómo fue la ?
ok what this is what did we do here ?
entonces these are for the contracts to do that .
o_k .
this is new .
mmhm .
o_k .
this is new .
.
right .
and he paid it off or ?
he paid it off .
yes .
so a este no más hay que hacerle copia .
y mandarlo de nuevo .
o_k perfect .
o_k another thing .
mmhm .
I need to know if anything new has been done within the last two weeks .
so we can keep track of it in the binder book .
o_k .
alright yeah I've been writing them here .
you've been doing them here ?
o_k .
yeah .
yeah I've been writing them here .
ok but how do you know if it' new ?
like .
right that' what I'm saying .
I'll have to find figure out if it' new .
I know this one was new .
mmhm .
Mayra o Tina .
estos no eran nuevos .
hubo algunos que se pusieron ...
mmhm .
aquí .
laugh .
so we'll see here cause we have an idea .
ah o_k .
mmhm .
.
teléfono ese .
o_k .
the last new .
o_k wait .
Ricardo Hernández .
mmhm .
we did .
is he there ?
sí Ricardo Hernandez is here somewhere on here .
nope .
he' not .
because Ricardo Hernández we did under me .
oh .
y yo no lo escribí .
I don't know this is under what still ?
this is under ...
Ana ?
yeah .
.
o_k .
then we did Kelly Flores .
mmhm .
no but I don't have that here .
unless it' pero qué .
which was three five .
I wonder if it' Col if it' Colleen no ?
ah no perdón .
pero three five is here .
mira .
o_k .
mira Ricardo Hernández .
ya lo tenía .
Ricardo Hernández .
aha .
y cuál era el otro ?
o_k .
Kelly Flores ?
Kelly Flores .
ah that one I don't see here .
no .
Rosa María Salgado .
that one ...
is there .
yes Salgado right there .
: Catalina Loango ?
sí esa está ahí Catalina .
o_k .
ah .
that' it .
mmhm .
after that that' it .
so Kelly Flores .
yeah so we need to find out .
.
bye .
thank you .
sí verdad .
hasta luego .
.
so anything under Cata after Catalina because maybe some of those are renewals .
o_k .
ajá .
I'm not sure .
sí sí .
sí, no todos son nuevos .
they're not all new .
.
you're very welcome .
are you better feeling better ?
.
yes .
well you don't look better laugh .
no you shoulda seen her Friday .
.
oh my god .
ay thank you .
I know they're very nice .
yes they're brown .
.
they're super .
como se están usando los zapatos esos así .
yeah .
gorgeous right ?
I got these at Banana_republic on sale .
really ?
on like a clearance .
you know oh my god when I was in Orlando I went to the premium outlets .
mmhm .
and we went to Banana_republic .
oh my god the men' shirts were like seven dollars .
the las camisetas de mujeres diez dólares .
mmhm .
oh my god I was like loving life laugh .
sí .
squeal !
they were super nice .
man that I had I had never been to that l outlet pero qué nice .
.
really ?
Coach they had the Coach .
.
did you go to the Coach ?
oh my god I was dying .
did you buy anything ?
no but I was dying .
pero es que tú sabes no era tan barato como you know ?
.
no it' not that cheap because they're still like two hundred a hundred and eighty .
exactly .
they're still up there .
but you know that I saw your little coin purse the little one you showed me .
.
it was nineteen dollars .
they were so cute yeah .
which one ?
.
a little coin purse .
ah porque estaba ahí guardado .
.
ay qué cómica .
mira they're super cute .
oh !
yo la vi en negra .
en este color no lo tenía .
.
yeah yeah .
where did you buy that one ?
.
but you bought that in an outlet too right ?
you know you know that they have an outlet in Sawgrass ?
.
which outlet ?
here ?
.
oh in Orlando .
but they have .
.
they have a Sawgrass outlet .
claro .
yeah I've got enough I've got enough .
did you know that ?
they have a what ?
an outlet ?
an outlet in Sawgrass .
of the Coach outlet ?
really ?
.
yo hace años que no voy a Sawgrass because it' so far for me now .
I've never been there .
I've been there once or twice .
.
I used to work around there .
so yo iba for lunch .
it was like something common .
mmhm .
y después que me mudé forget it that' it .
it' been more than a year .
.
I know I know .
I have a gazillion Coach purses .
I need I need I need to like alternate them .
.
because cuando I have a lot of them .
but cuando la cojo con una that' the one that I wear for like : .
yo también yo también .
.
pero you know what it is for me ?
at least I find que in my closet they're not organized so that I can actually change them .
you know I have to take down the box change my purse entonces ya no me da ganas de cambiarla .
I bought um un little estante de esos de like Tupperware that has two drawers .
ajá .
and then I shoved them there .
but still and I look at the damn thing everday .
laugh .
.
and I'm like ...
yes yesterday I was looking for something .
and I said +"/.
+" oh look I'm going to bring this one tomorrow .
and look I brought the same one .
no yo soy igual .
yo cuando la cojo con uno forget it .
yeah .
.
oh I never take off my ear_rings .
mmhm .
right .
.
yeah .
yeah I never take mine off ever ever ever .
.
no me neither .
never .
oh yeah speaking of did did you go pick up your bracelet at the place ?
no they didn't call me yet .
I wasn't sure .
oh .
I have to call today .
he called you ?
no but I remembered .
and I was like I wonder if she went ?
no porque como ...
no yo tengo el tiquecito .
we're gonna go maybe this afternoon .
you said it was by one fifty second right ?
I have the address and everything like that .
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah .
sí no yo lo pensé el otro día .
and I was going to ask you .
and then I forgot .
mm .
so I thought maybe he was gonna call here you know ?
pero since I wasn't here laugh .
yeah .
so ...
alright so so anything under Catalina Loango ...
alright so then we need to figure out who' new from there on .
and then just put it in here so we have a record .
mmhm .
and then whatever whatever' Ana I I did her initials so so that we know .
ah o_k o_k .
o_k o_k .
you know it' that or whatever .
so esto no más que es nuevo ?
esto es only new .
only new ?
I don't put homeowner renewals in here .
o_k .
I don't .
If it' an auto renewal and we do it then yes .
mmhm .
o_k .
but other than that it' just new new stuff or commercial and whatever .
sí nada más o_k .
o_k .
so esto yo lo ...
o_k so yes .
so I'll figure that out then .
so we gotta keep this out yeah .
ajá .
y lo pongo esto aquí para hacer eso .
then what else ?
so entonces these things are new .
and I just have to make sure to make copies of the things .
and then I'll put the the contracts to the side the finance contracts .
and then we'll do that new .
yes .
o_k y eso ya creo que estaba aquí yes ?
esto .
no .
I don't know .
there was something here .
I have to go pee .
este yo lo vi por aquí también .
dejáme ver cuál es el laugh ...
.
un empleado nuevo .
laugh look that' Leah' husband .
.
how are you ?
está ahí coloreando .
.
he' a he' he él encanta pintar .
he paints really really nice .
.
yeah .
he' really really nice .
entonces dejáme ver what else I need to do .
.
he estado once minutos hablando .
yo laugh .
.
yeah .
eleven minutes .
.
but yeah this is hers ?
yeah .
.
so what did you guys do on the weekend ?
uhuh .
.
wow .
oh I love it .
.
wow .
what two sides ?
.
yeah .
you know él él él tiene la cosa esa negra ahí .
.
they were um pretending to be football players .
they would pretend to be football players .
but of course they did it with permanent marker .
.
that' crazy .
yo traté I was like rubbing it pero no .
.
so no no va él .
baseball players and football players and ...
.
and there was three of them porque era él el hermano y Selina' son .
I know that one is super cute .
.
yeah .
yes .
.
so these are all the new ones .
ajá exacto .
sí yo lo voy a hacer las copias .
I'm going to check the the before I send anything out I'm .
.
exactly exactly .
dale por eso te pregunto .
.
o_k .
and no that' why I had asked you if Sabrina called because I had left her a message for um the pictures .
I need the pictures for that Ricardo Hernández guy .
.
we got the payment on the credit card .
pero .
.
yes yeah it' it' mailed out .
and then Citizens sent me that fax thing that they sent .
so they needed the pictures .
and they needed um her phone number .
.
so I put the phone number on the mismo papel .
pero le tengo que mandar la foto .
.
and that' the message that I left her .
exactly porque eso es lo del mensaje so she' aware of it .
yeah so ...
.
did you guys make up already ?
so that' that .
did you guys make up ?
entonces esto I have to figure out what this is .
where it' coming from .
.
a sharpener ?
no idea papi .
let me see .
no creo papi .
.
I don't think I have a sharpener here .
ya almorzaron ?
bueno pero van van a venir a una a una hora decente ?
let me check but I don't think I do .
.
you have to go ?
ah o_k .
yeah .
alright .
well .
.
twelve fifty .
las cuatro .
.
no tenemos black ?
ah no sé .
.
no .
no this is this is a black one .
pero you have to be careful .
no lo apretes mucho abajo .
.
ajá .
oh o_k .
.
yeah .
oh o_k .
o_k mamá .
o_k o_k .
you did it ?
cool .
.
yeah .
no no tampoco así pero bueno .
o_k o_k that' fine .
o_k bye bye .
alright so what are we doing now ?
.
o_k .
bueno ya .
so what else ?
no ya .
so ya .
I already figured it out .
I'm just gonna go through this .
make sure we have everything .
make the copies .
separate the the finance agreements .
o_k .
and then you know put them back there .
y este I'll have to see what the heck .
o_k .
and then I asked her .
mmhm .
porque abajo de ahí yo me había encontrado todo .
there' a little more stuff down there .
yo esto también estaba aquí .
yes .
esto .
all this yeah .
this was all here .
so it' that new stuff ?
is it old stuff ?
what is it ?
this is pretty new stuff this is pretty new things that I have opened up .
o_k .
yeah pero bueno esos son premiums too .
mira Fra el Francisco ese que that was that' the file that' there .
o_k .
but I have to figure out what it is .
because I wasn't sure .
yeah .
and then this thing this nightmare that just doesn't go away .
mmhm .
oh sí el de Luz .
yeah here' the thing .
mmhm .
oh wait this is mine .
this says x .
right .
o_k it does it' not giving me a base flood zone .
but it wants it .
mm .
so I don't know what numbers esta esta otra mujer puso allá adentro .
so then .
sí porque entonces how do we know it' gonna be the same amount right ?
exactly .
and then also : the lender' requesting flood insurance even though property is in x zone .
mmhm .
pero why if it' in I I don't understand if it' in you know ...
right .
why ?
and then .
like he' doing it like a precaution .
pero how do we know that ?
exactly .
and then what' the value ?
what' the charge on it right ?
we need the appraisal no ?
what' the amount ?
yeah .
we don't know .
we don't .
I mean .
sí porque supuestamente nosotros teníamos un code o algo que fue lo que nosotros le mandamos .
o esto .
exactly .
pero adónde está ?
because that was from .
I don't know if that' still in the computer .
I doubt very much .
sí yo lo dudo .
y era nada más que twenty eight thousand building ?
yeah .
if if you do a quote without those numbers and only that building would it come up too at one eighty eight or ?
the only thing that I'm thinking is that she did that preferred que the preferred is in an x zone .
mmhm .
entonces no te piden elevación .
oh .
that' the only thing .
pero que ...
and we can do that or ?
yeah yeah .
we can do that ourselves so we don't need that .
when when you go in on basic standard it says standard quotes .
I think this one it says preferred something or the other .
en el mismo U_S_Security no ?
yeah .
yeah yeah .
it' down here .
yeah because I checked this already to Us_security so .
ah verdad verdad verdad .
you're exactly right .
three three three .
.
now ?
o_k now go to where it says quote .
no o_k .
the P_R_P application the second one there .
P_R_P oh .
preferred no ?
mmhm .
preferred something preferred risk .
no sé qué más .
entonces ahí does I does answer all of the questions ?
yeah just put right do that .
o_k .
and then just figure out how to .
yeah .
insurance hello .
yes she' right here .
hold on one second .
it' your mom .
ya si quieres vete si ya yo lo hago sola .
no no no I don't mind .
ya después yo lo hago sola o sea ya no ya no más una .
ajá ?
faltan dos minuticos .
two minutes I'll do it myself laugh .
alright so property address is what ?
oh you want Ana to go deposit at Ocean Bank first ?
it' : just a little bit down the street .
it' it' it' by it' by Bank United .
on west eleventh street .
o_k ?
property city Miami .
o_k o_k let me get it ready for you .
o_k thanks bye .
property state shoot .
.
alright let' see .
let' try it again .
address .
.
northwest eleventh street .
Miami Florida .
is building located in ?
no .
do any of the following conditions arise to the ?
.
no .
last name Villegas .
Villegas .
first name is what ?
.
number .
el teléfono dónde está ?
aló .
el teléfono .
.
grunt I don't have his number .
uhuh .
.
yeah you know what somebody else .
no yeah .
.
of property .
mmhm loan number .
first first bank account number .
.
first bank account number .
insurance .
buenas tardes .
sí .
o_k .
no espérese .
y cuál es el apellido ?
Medina ?
y la carta dice dígame otra vez ?
.
usted tenía una cancelación pendiente o algo porque eso quiere decir que ya se está está bien como que ya se reinstaló no no no va a cancelar .
sí exacto .
sí rescission como que ya está que esto sabe que que si estaba en cancelación que ya lo lo arreglaron lo que ...
o_k la dirección is for two thousand and four Northwest Franklin Street .
o_k .
pero dice notice of rescission no ?
that deme un segundito .
déjeme mirar aquí un momentico o_k ?
déjame buscarlo espérese .
o_k .
en total que van a sacar son ciento dieciséis cincuenta .
three zero nine five four seven .
yeah .
I can't find it .
.
cuál es el número de la póliza en el papel ?
cero seis tres nueve .
+, ajá .
o_k .
y el account number ?
dame un segundito .
o_k .
muy bien .
ajá .
.
Ana ?
what does this mean ?
notice of rescission .
.
Antonio García .
dice que no recibieron el down payment .
.
cool .
did you get what you were looking for ?
porque él me está llamando porque recibió esa carta .
pero what is .
.
yeah .
what does that mean ?
.
o_k .
o_k I'll get his number .
.
o_k .
señor Medina ?
deme su número .
déjeme llamar a la compañía a ver de qué se trata exactamente .
y yo lo llamo .
oh .
claro claro sí yo lo veo aquí .
no sé por qué le habrá mandado eso .
.
deme un número dónde yo le puedo regresar la llamada .
y déjame llamar a la compañía directamente .
o_k .
tres dos uno mmhm .
o_k señor Medina .
mmhm ?
que tienes que hacer el pago .
no lo has recibido .
o_k .
no .
sí .
déjame averiguar .
y si es usted tiene acceso al fax ?
o_k cualquier cosa usted me da el número .
y yo le mando los cupones directamente .
o_k ?
yo deme un ratico .
y yo le averiguo de qué está pasando .
yo lo llamo en seguidita .
.
claro claro que no .
no no se preocupe .
bueno y gracias .
hasta luego .
.
no llega qué ?
oh really ?
.
did you send .
did you finally do the invoice ?
.
oh .
yeah .
.
awesome .
alright so I did that already now I'm doing this .
flood zone .
ex occupancy single family .
.
number of floors single floor .
oh thank you papi .
let me see .
wow !
Spiderman !
ooh Halo that' the Halo one ?
.
oh that' right .
cool .
and the flowers .
oh and the turtle !
gasp .
.
wow .
those are ants ?
.
wow .
right here mama .
.
super nice .
I'm gonna put it right there .
.
oh yeah ?
you should sign it here so everybody know who did it .
so you .
however you like to sign papi .
how do you like to sign ?
.
Timmy ?
just down the street down that way .
.
thank you .
sorry .
.
the building .
ah ?
.
today is three thirty one .
march thirty first three thirty one .
ay dios mío I don't know .
alright .
Timothy Ceballos super nice .
put it right here .
.
um .
espérate aquí hay una .
let' see .
insurance .
o_k ?
no it' fine .
who' calling ?
yeah I'd like to see it .
but you know what you really need to get to me because you're homeowner .
o_k .
yeah we're open .
we're here until five o'clock .
you're welcome .
right .
alright so I have to throw this out .
o_k .
alright let me get you another paper .
yes take this one for now .
the insurance ?
aha .
.
laugh yeah .
madre .
insurance .
yeah .
I'm yeah I'm insurance .
ah o_k sí yeah .
sí porque yo no veía nada aquí pero it doesn't it said that we never got the deposit .
that' what it said on mine like well like they never got the deposit or down payment .
and he' like +"/.
+" cómo que .
o sea yo no le dije eso pero he' like +"/.
+" no pero cómo no va a tener seguro .
+" si yo di como setecientos y pico dólares ?
ah cómo no .
no se preocupe .
yo voy a averiguar whatever .
o_k o_k mom .
I'll put it here .
alright .
o_k o_k .
bueno bye .